var questions = [
    {
        question: "What is the first line of dialogue in Iron Man, the very first MCU film?",
        choices: ["I feel like you're driving me to a court-marshal.", "I am Iron Man", "Is it cool if I take a picture with you?"],
        answer: "I feel like you're driving me to a court-marshal"
    },
    {
        question: "What video game is Thor addicted to in Avengers: Endgame?",
        choices: ["World of Warcraft", "Fortnite", "Rocket League"],
        answer: "Fortnite"
    },
    {
        question: "Which film did Black Panther first appear in?",
        choices: ["Black Panther", "Captain America: Civil War", "Captain America: The Winter Soldier"],
        answer: "Captain America: Civil War"
    },
    {
        question: "Where does Ant-Man get stuck at the end of Ant-Man and the Wasp?",
        choices: ["Wakanda", "The Quantum Realm", "In space"],
        answer: "The Quantum Realm"
    },
    {
        question: "In Captain Marvel, what kind of alien is Groose the Cat?",
        choices: ["Chitauri", "Flerken", "Sakaaran"],
        answer: "Flerken"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the amulet Dr. Strange wears around his neck?",
        choices: ["The Orb of the Ancient One", "The Eye of Agamotto", "The Relic of Kamar-Taj"],
        answer: "The Eye of Agamotto"
    },
    {
        question: "What song does Baby Groot dance to at the end of Guardians of the Galaxy?",
        choices: ["Ain't No Mountain High Enough - Marvin Gaye", "I Want You Back - Jackson 5", "Moonage Daydream - David Bowie"],
        answer: "I Want You Back - Jackson 5"
    },
    {
        question: "In the post-credit scene, what food do the Avengers eat after the Battle of New York?",
        choices: ["Shawarma", "Chinese", "Sushi"],
        answer: "Shawarma"
    },
    {
        question: "The final battle between Spider-Man and Mysterio takes place on which bridge?",
        choices: ["Waterloo Bridge", "London Bridge", "Tower Bridge"],
        answer: "London Bridge"
    },
    {
        question: "In Captain America: The First Avenger, what does Steve Rogers say when asked if he wants to kill Nazi's?",
        choices: ["I'd kill and die for my country", "Who doesn't?", "I don't like bullies, I don't care where they're from"],
        answer: "I don't like bullies, I don't care where they're from"
    }
];